翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Let's kick today off with a puzzle that's going to be really important to us to understand how to build a list.
今天让我们从一个谜题开始，如何建立一个链表
So this right here, there's a website address up here for answering the question.
这里有一个用来回答问题的网址
That doesn't apply if you're only watching the videos online.
如果你只在网上看视频，那就没用了
That's something for students who are there in the live lectures.
这是为现场听课的学生准备的
So don't worry about that.
所以别担心
So this puzzle is a puzzle that I haven't told you how to answer yet,
这个谜题我还没告诉你们该如何回答
but I want you to try and use your intuition or whatever background knowledge that you may have to answer it.
我想让你凭直觉或任何背景知识回答它
So what I have here is Walrus a equals new Walrus.
这里有 Walrus a = new Walrus()
And these are a couple of parameters that are the Walrus's weight and tusk size,
这些参数是海象（Walrus）的重量和象牙的大小
but it doesn't much matter.
但无关紧要
Here, we have Walrus b, and we say b equals a and then change the weight of b.
这里有海象 b，让 b = a，然后改变 b 的重量
So the question I have for you is,
我要问的是
knowing that b was set equal to a,
已知 b = a
does this change to be affect a?
这一变化会影响 a 吗？
And so we're going to print these out to get the answer.
我们要把这些打印出来，才能得到答案
And so if you're not sure, that's fine.
所以如果你不确定也没关系
But what I want you to do now is pause the video and think really carefully about what you think the answer might be.
但请暂停视频，仔细思考问题的答案
Maybe try writing it out on paper.
也许可以试着写在纸上
And then I'll reveal the answer.
稍后我会揭晓答案
So pause and think.
暂停想一想
So it turns out the answer is yes, it does change the Walrus.
答案是肯定的，这的确改变了海象
Changing b's weight does affect both Walruses, both a,
改变 b 的体重确实会影响 a
which is printed first, and b, even though a's weight was originally set to 1,000.
a 首先被打印，然后是 b，即使 a 的重量最初被设为1000
Why? Well, we'll get there in a moment.
为什么？我们马上揭晓
But I have another puzzle for you before we get there.
在那之前我还有另一个谜题要问你
Let's talk about integers.
整型怎么样
Let's say we have an integer x and we set it equal to 5,
假设整型 x 设为5
create another integer y, and then say y equals x, and then change x.
创建另一个整型 y，然后假设 y = x，再更改 x
So the question now is, will the change to x affect y?
问题是，对 x 的改变会影响 y 吗？
And we're going to print them out to see what happens.
打印出来看看会发生什么
And again, I haven't told you everything you need to know to answer this question,
再说一次，我没有告诉你们回答这个问题所需要知道的一切
so make your best guess and I will let you know.
所以尽力猜，我会让你明白的
So it turns out the answer is it does not affect y.
答案是它不影响 y
And why is that?
为什么会这样呢？
Well, I'm going to give you a visual picture using the visualizer,
我要用 visualizer 给你一张可视化图片
but we're going to actually spend some time really picking this apart
但是我们要花点时间区分它们
and building a foundation that's going to be really crucial to our understanding of data structures moving forwards.
建立一个对理解数据结构至关重要的基础
So let's run this in the visualizer.
在 visualizer 中运行它
And so, after I create this Walrus, I have a Walrus a.
创造海象后，就有了一个海象 a
And then, when I say b equals a, what we notice is that, visually, we have two arrows pointing at the same Walrus.
然后执行 b = a 时，我们注意到两个箭头指向同一只海象
So in some sense, a and b for whatever reason are the same Walrus.
所以在某种意义上，不管怎样 a 和 b 都是相同的海象
And so, if I do b.weight, that single walrus is going to have its weight changed.
所以调用 b.weight，这只海象的体重就会改变
And so printing it out, no big surprise,
所以打印的结果也就不足为奇了
is going to have the same result for both.
两者结果相同
How about the integer case?
整型的情况呢？
Well, when I say int x equals 5, I have a number 5 in this box.
当执行 int x = 5，这个盒子里有一个数字5
I see y equals x.
执行 y = x
And so now, I have the number 5 in this box as well.
这个盒子中也有了数字5
And now, when I say x equals 2, well, these are two totally different boxes.
现在执行 x = 2，这是两个完全不同的盒子
It's not like an arrow pointing at something.
跟箭头指向不同
So when I do x equals 2, it's only going to change this right here.
所以执行 x = 2 时，只会改变这个值
And so printing them out, I get no change to y in response to x's change.
打印结果表明，y 没有随着 x 改变而改变
So what we're going to do next is really pick that apart,
下一步要做的就是把它们区别开
but that's the visual picture you might have in mind that helps to explain it.
但记住这个可视化图片，会对理解有帮助
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）